

FERRY ANDESKA

Data Entry Front-End Developer

PROFILE

I'm Ferry Andeska, 25 years old. A PIC of data entry at GDILab.com, specification as quality control data for database. In charge of checking the accuracy, completeness and correctness data from the database, maintanance machine Server, maintan exist clients & approaching new clients.

SOCIAL



@fandeska_



@fandeska



Ferry Andeska



+6281298771542

SOFTWARE



HTML 5



A Adobe Illustrator



B Bootstrap 5 CSS 3





MySQL Database

EDUCATION

2014 - 2015 Gunadarma University, Depok.

Bachelor Degree of Information Systems.

2010 - 2013 Gunadarma University, Depok.

Diploma Degree of Informatics Management.

OTHERS

Organization Experiences As ManPower Events at Sial InterFood Jakarta, Mega Career Expo Jakarta, Jakarta Marathon, IdeaFest, Young On Top Conference 2017 and many more.

EXPERIENCE

Data Entry (Person In Charge) 14th Des 2015 - Now PT. Generasi Digital Internasional (GDILab.com) Kemang, Jakarta. A Social Media Analytic & Monitoring TV / Radio

Funding Officer 28th Sep 2015 – 27th Nov 2015 Bank Tabungan Negara (BTN) Citeureup, Bogor.

